( Ethereal music )
♪ ♪
What 's up , Claire ?
Hey .
So this is it , huh ?
Just you and me .
End of days ...
Ha .
Yeah .
Uh , have you talked to Ron lately ?
Ron is in Barbados snorkeling for the ever-elusive
Double Back Saddle Fish
and he left explicit instructions not to be disturbed .
Yeah , well , if you owned this place you 'd be off to Barbados , too .
Sure , I would . Especially if I had two saps back at home
waiting to cover for me .
Oh , did you get your camera fixed ?
No , it 's totaled .
I have to send it back to Pana-suck-ass .
I have my microphones though ,
so we can make do with EVP investigations .
OK .
Oh hey , that reminds me .
I have to show you something .
So ..
I was trolling around on some of the paranormal forums last night
and I came across something pretty interesting .
You 're definitely gonna wanna see this .
What is it ?
Hold on . Just watch ...
Look closely ...
I missed it the first time ...
It 's gonna blow your mind ...
It 's really heavy ...
( Demonic screech )
You bastard !
So good !
Oh my God . Every time .
Oh my god .
( Laughs )
( Inhaler puff )
What room did you take ?
Uh ... 216 .
Of course .
Hey , I 've been here since last night .
That 's just the way it goes .
225 is taken ,
other than that it 's pretty much wide open .
Second floor only though , remember ?
Third floor is already done .
Only one guest ? Brutal .
Eh , it doesn 't take a genius to figure out
why this place is going out of business .
Hm .
OK , I 'll take room 214 .
I figured we 'd take seven to seven shifts .
Something like that ...
Alright . Sounds good .
I 'll bring it back down .
( Desk bell rings )
( Ethereal music )
♪ ♪
OK , sweetie .
Come here .
OK .
( Sighs )
( TV switches on )
( Old movie plays )
OK , if I could just get you to sign that .
Here 's your room key , number 224 .
You wanna head up to the top of the stairs
and take a right and another quick right ,
sorta like a dog leg .
And then you go about halfway down the hallway
and it 's on the right hand side .
You can 't miss it .
Thank you .
Do you know who that is ?
It 's Leanne Reese-Jones .
OK .
She was the mom on " Like Mother Like Son " !
Dude , she 's super-famous .
OK , whatever .
Man ...
Leanne Rease-Jones ...
I wonder what she 's doing here .
She 's guest-speaking at some convention in Pottstown .
How do you know that ?
She told me .
What ?
What else did she tell you ?
Nothing . Why are you acting so weird ?
I 'm not .
Well , here 's her autograph . Just relax .
Whatever . Why are you being so grouchy today ?
I 'm not . I 'm just stressed .
This site is killing me .
Let me see it .
Mm ...
( Scrolling mouse )
It looks good .
I hate web design .
It looks really good .
I like the little ghosts .
It 's not the most professional , but it 's not bad .
There 's a lot of money in this right now .
I just ... I have to act fast .
Looks really good .
I like it .
And , you know , once we get some proof on there ,
it won 't matter what it looks like .
Hey , so I was thinking .
It seems like when something really creepy happens ,
nobody else is around , right ?
Like every time you 've seen stuff , you were alone .
So ...
I was just thinking that since the hotel is practically empty ,
we might have a chance of making some real contact .
Does that makes sense ?
Yeah .
Yeah . I think this weekend 's gonna be it .
We 're gonna get something good . I can feel it .
- What ? - What ?
What ?
What ... ?
( Phone rings )
Front desk .
Yes , Ms. Reese-Jones .
Oh , sure . I 'll send them right up for you .
You 're welcome .
I forgot to stock the towels .
I 'll get them .
Good , save me the ulcer .
That Gayle in 225 is driving me nuts
and I don 't want her to see me .
Oooh , that lady with the kid ?
I know , what 's her deal ?
She was giving me total agro vibes upstairs .
She had a huge fight with her husband
and she 's staying here ' til Sunday with her son as payback .
She 's having a very hard time
and she wants him to realize how hard his life is without her .
How do you know all that ?
She told me .
Why do you seem so surprised that I talk to the guests ?
Um-hm
Go on , superfan . Don 't keep the talent waiting .
( Front desk bell rings )
( Knocking )
Miss Rease-Jones ?
I have your towels ...
( Shower running )
Miss Rease-Jones ?
Oh , be a lamb and hand me one of those ...
Thank you .
You 're welcome , Miss Rease-Jones .
( Shower turns off )
Call me Lee .
Ok .
What 's your name , sweetheart ?
Claire
You 're a life saver , Claire .
Oh , no no ... I couldn 't . I couldn 't
Come on . You 'll hurt an old lady 's feelings .
Thanks , Miss , uh , Lee .
I 'm a really big fan of yours !
" Like Mother Like Son " was one of my all time favorite shows ,
and you were amazing in it
and in ' The Waking of Eleanor ...
I love that film .
Yeah , I used to watch it all the time growing up with my mom .
Leven used to put my hair in , like , little braids , like you did .
I mean , they never looked as good though .
Well , thank you .
That 's very nice of you to say .
And what do you do , Claire ?
I work at the front desk .
So if there 's anything else that you need , just let me know .
I mean , this is our last weekend open
so Luke and I are the only ones on staff today .
Yeah , we 're actually sleeping here instead of going home .
It 's pretty crazy .
I meant in life .
Are you an aspiring actress ?
Is that what makes you such an astute fan of my work ?
Me ?
No ... I just work at the hotel .
Oh ...
But ... I 'm kinda like ... you know .. in between ... stuff .
OK ...
Uh , Claire ...
The towels .
Right .
Of course , yes .
There you go .
How did it go ?
You two gonna collaborate on something ?
She kind of made me feel like an asshole .
Well , she 's an actress .
What 's that supposed to mean ?
And what do you know about actresses anyway ?
I don 't know a lot ,
but I do know a little bit about a lot of things ...
Ugh , why did she have to be such a bummer ?
And why do you have to be so negative ? !
I 'm not negative , I 'm a realist . There 's a difference .
You 're pessimistic .
Pessimism is just a higher form of optimism .
If you expect nothing from people ,
then you go through life being pleasantly surprised .
Yeah , well , nobody loves an albatross .
I 'm going to get some coffee . You want anything ?
I do not .
Fine !
( Inhaler puff )
Hey , how 's it going ?
What can I get for you ?
Um ... ah ...
I 'll tell you what . You take your time
and if you have any questions , just let me know .
Doesn 't a cyclops always have one eye ?
What do you mean ?
Never mind .
Um , I will have a large soy mocha latte with a pump of caramel .
Good choice .
So , uh , how are things going next door ?
Uh ... fine .
( Coffee machine sputters )
Can I speak frankly with you ?
I mean , I know we don 't know each other that well but
I see you all the time and we 're all girls here .
This Sunday , my boyfriend is taking me on a picnic to the bay
and I 'm really excited .
I know it 's going to be super-romantic ,
and I think that
I 'm not letting myself be fully excited
because there 's something in our relationship that 's been bothering me ,
which is that we 've been together for almost a year
and he still has not told me that he loves me .
And I just need to talk to somebody about it because
I don 't want to ask him to tell me . I mean , he said it on IM .
That 's the thing , he said it on IM .
Which my friend says doesn 't count .
It 's like saying " I love you " during sex .
It doesn 't count .
And so I wonder if ...
Where 's your coffee ?
They ran out .
Is that annoying girl still there ?
Ugh . Yes .
What a fail-blog .
Epic .
Do you ever think about when you dropped out of college
and wonder if you made the right choice ?
Every day .
Why do people have such high expectations ?
Everything happens for a reason , Claire .
Nobody just ends up at the Yankee Pedlar .
I guess .
You know what really gets me though ?
Hold that thought .
My eyes feel like they 've been doused in Tapatio .
I need to go upstairs .
What ?
I 'm sorry , I 'm dead .
We can talk about your upcoming quarter-life crisis tomorrow .
I just need to tap out right now .
Fine .
Leave your computer though .
What ? I 'm not gonna hack the system .
I just wanna look up a pair of high tops .
And it gets really boring when there 's nobody else at the hotel .
And my book sucks .
OK . Just be careful with it .
Duh .
Oh and if you get the itch to do any recording ,
the recorder is charging in the back office .
You remember how to use it you just plug the microphone into the ...
I know how to do it . I get it .
Geez . I 'd hate to be a ghost in this hotel tonight .
Goodnight , Claire .
Good night , Luke .
( Clock chimes )
( Sighs )
Where is your website ?
( Scoffs )
Wow , don 't forget to remind him about this .
( Door creaking shut )
Oh .
Tragedy .
Kinda creepy .
( Bang )
( Louder bang )
Whoa .
Shit .
How do you work this thing ?
( Bang )
( Banging continues )
I don 't wanna scare you but I 'm standing right behind you .
Fuck ! What the fuck ?
Oh my God !
Jesus Christ ! You scared the shit out of me !
- What are you doing over here anyway ? - Crap !
I thought I heard a noise , dude !
Like what ?
Banging . Like a banging , man . Ugh !
- OK , well , - God .
I woke up and couldn 't go back to sleep .
So we can switch now if you want .
Fuck ! Ok ! God !
God !
Sorry .
Ugh !
Fuck !
( Laughs )
My heart is pounding .
Do you know the story of Madeline O 'Malley ?
She was the woman that died here in the hotel .
She hung herself
after her fiancée stood her up on their wedding day .
The original owners of the hotel
thought it would be bad press and hurt the business .
So they hid her dead body in the wood cellar for three days
before they could smuggle her out on the loading bay .
When the people of the town finally figured out
what had happened here ,
they were outraged .
So the owners of the hotel had to close it down
and were forced to sell it .
Nobody came through here again until the sixties .
And , ever since then ,
people have reported seeing the ghost of Madeline O 'Malley .
Roaming the hallways , waiting for her lover .
Some say she 's even looking to take up a new one .
Excuse me ?
What are you doing ?
Mommy !
What 's going on ?
She said there 's a ghost in the hotel !
She says it 's coming to get me !
I never said that !
What is the matter with you ?
He 's just a child .
Sweetie ?
Sweetie .
It 's OK . It 's not real .
Just a story , OK ?
All right ? Come here .
( Kisses forehead )
I don 't need this .
I have enough going on in my life .
Yes , ma 'am .
You OK ?
And you . We still need towels .
I am tired of asking .
Don 't make me the bad guy in this .
Right .
We 're in room 225 .
Yeah , I know which room you 're in .
I work in the hotel .
Come on , sweetie . It 's a silly story , right ?
You OK ?
Ay yi yi .
Oh , I bought that cheap bread . I can taste it .
Never skimp on bread .
You 'll always regret it .
So , why do you think she sticks around here ?
Beats me .
Our rates aren 't that cheap .
The Courtyard by Marriot on Route 13 is much better .
No , not her .
I mean Madeline .
What do you think she wants ?
I don 't know .
I don 't spend too much time trying to figure out what women want .
Especially dead ones .
Please ...
Well , when you saw her , what did she look like ?
Like , was she all dead-looking ?
The thing about physical encounters is
you don 't really remember the details .
It 's weird because you think you would but its like
she was there one minute and gone the next .
It 's almost like she was never even there at all .
I don 't know . It 's hard to explain . You kind of just had to be there .
God , I 'm so jealous .
But if I saw her I probably would 've freaked out .
( Chuckles )
I can 't believe you never had your camera with you .
I know . It kills me .
You down for some recording tonight ?
Mm ... definitely .
We 've gotta find some proof that Madeline O 'Malley exists
before this place closes down . We have to .
Imagine how she feels , being stuck here forever .
We gotta get something on tape .
It 's like a moral imperative .
( Groans in disgust )
Eh !
( Big sigh )
( Trash bag leaks )
Oh my God .
Ick !
Hi , Lee !
( Scoffs )
( Scraping noise )
( Scraping noise continues )
( Screams )
( Inhaler puff )
Shit !
How 'd you get in there , bird ?
Luke .
Luke , you are not going to believe what just happened to me .
Luke ?
( Toilet flushes )
What ?
Uh ... never mind .
I 'm a pumpkin .
I 'm gonna kill the snake .
Don 't forget to record .
I left the list for you on the desk .
OK .
Enjoy your internet porn .
( Scoffs )
This is EVP recording of the laundry room .
( Room tone )
( Static )
Luke , I 'm skipping this one .
There 's nothing in here .
This is the EVP recording of the banquet room .
I 'm trying to contact the spirit of Madeline O 'Malley .
Madeline , if you can hear me , please give us a sign .
( Room tone )
( Static garbles )
Damnit , Luke , you said this thing would be set up .
( Static hiss )
( Whisper in static )
( Distant piano playing )
( Piano playing )
( Static hiss )
( Piano playing gets louder )
( Piano stops )
( Static hiss )
( Piano chord )
Luke !
Luke , Come on ! Wake up !
Come on ! Wake up ! Wake up ! Wake up !
Hold it , hold it , hold it !
Luke !
Coming ! Jesus Christ .
What the eff ?
Claire , I still have , like , two hours left , man !
Dude ! You have to listen to this !
The piano was playing by itself !
I think it was her !
Come on , I 'll be down at seven .
I 'll listen to it then .
No ! No , I 'm scared !
OK , come in .
Shit .
Uh ... actually ...
I 'm ... OK ...
You sure ?
Yeah , I think I just freaked out for a minute but I 'll ...
I 'll be fine .
OK .
Well , I 'll be down in a few hours , alright ?
( Sighs )
Do you mind keeping it down ?
Do I have to ask you again ?
You know what ?
Just back off , OK ? !
You 're asking me what I " do " the other day ?
Well , I just recorded an unexplainable phenomenon !
There is a ghost in this hotel
and I got it on tape and it 's a big deal !
So just ... Leave me alone !
Come with me for a moment .
Here , sit .
You need a drink .
Cheers .
( Coughs )
( sass )
You alright ?
Mm-hmm .
Tell me about what you saw .
I ...
Look .
I 'm sorry about yesterday .
I have a tendency not to be a nice person .
I know that .
Please don 't take it personally .
I don 't apologize more than once .
Look , I can help you with what you 're looking for .
I just need to know what it is that you 're looking for .
I 'm sorry .
Help me with ... what ?
Do you know what this is ?
It 's a pendulum .
It 's used to answer life 's more ... difficult questions .
Do you know why I 'm here ?
You 're speaking at an acting convention in Pottstown ?
No .
I 'm not here for acting .
I 'm here as a guest at a healers ' gathering .
That 's what I do now . It 's my true calling .
Claire , everything in this world is connected .
Whether we understand that or not depends on our sense of perception ,
our willingness to communicate .
Now , you want to communicate with the spirits in this hotel ?
I can help you do that .
I just need to know what it is that you want from them .
I don 't know .
If they 're real ?
The ... the ghosts ?
Spirits .
There is no real in this world , Claire .
It 's all a state of being .
There are no beginnings .
There are no ends .
There are no ghosts .
We 're each divine beings
that incorporate one energy in the universe .
Like , uh ...
Droplets of water in a vast ocean .
The universe has a plan for each and every one of us .
Now , I want you to ignore what your conscious mind tells you .
And open yourself up , OK ?
What is it that you want from these spirits ?
I want to know if it was
Madeline O 'Malley playing the piano downstairs .
And if she really is the spirit living in this hotel .
Hmm .
Ask again .
This time , close your eyes and really concentrate .
Open yourself up .
Really ask it . Ask it directly .
Are you the spirit of Madeline O 'Malley ?
Did you die in this hotel ?
Was that you playing the piano ?
They won 't say who they are .
They ?
There are three of them .
What do they want ?
Same thing you do .
What ?
To live .
But they 're not alive .
There was a terrible tragedy in this hotel .
Something about the basement .
A mistake ?
It 's her . It 's Madeline .
That 's where they hid her body .
You mustn 't go down into the basement .
Why ? Is that where she 's trapped ?
Is her spirit trapped in there ?
You can 't save her .
They tried to warn her . They tried to help her .
Who 's they ? What do they want ?
What happened ?
I lost contact .
( Sign squeaks )
( Shower turns off )
Luke .
No towels .
( Inhaler puff )
( Screaming )
( Alarm clock beeping )
( Screams )
Luke !
OK .
That 's it , I 've had enough .
We 're going back to your dad .
OK ?
Drink .
Don 't worry about Gozer and her demon seed leaving .
You actually did us a favor .
Claire , you 're really freaking me out .
You gotta pull it together .
You 're way out in the weeds right now .
It happened to me when I started messing around with this stuff .
You really gotta be careful about what 's going on up here .
You start thinking you 're seeing things and it might never stop .
OK , fine .
The dream is one thing .
But what about the piano ?
And what about everything that Lee said ?
I listened to the piano tape
and I don 't know what to tell you .
Maybe it 's explainable . Maybe it isn 't .
But it 's not worth getting yourself worked up over .
None of this is .
As for the kook upstairs ...
Look , Claire ,
how many times have you seen someone on late night TV
hawking their psychic wares to an audience full of rubes ?
Tons , right ?
And how many times have you seen a psychic in the newspaper ,
solving crimes or
healing someone without medicine or winning the lottery ?
Almost never , right ?
That 's because it 's all bullshit .
It 's hocus-pocus .
That woman upstairs is just an insecure old actress
and she 's just trying to stay relevant .
It 's pathetic .
OK .
Don 't you want to try to figure out what 's going on here ?
Why aren 't you more intrigued by this ?
I mean , this could be it .
This could be Madeline trying to make contact
and you just don 't even care .
Isn 't this supposed to be your deal ?
( Bell ringing )
I swear to God , if that bitch is back with her kid ...
Be cool .
Can I help you , sir ?
Yes , I 'd like a room for the night , please .
OK , just one night ?
Yes .
I 'd like Room 353 , please .
I 'm sorry , sir , that room 's not available right now .
We only have rooms available on the second floor
on account of this being our last weekend open .
No .
I must have Room 353 , please .
This is very important to me .
I came a long way .
Sir ?
All the rooms on the third floor have been stripped .
So if you don 't mind bringing up some sheets
and sleeping in a room without furniture then ...
I think we can help you out .
That would be fine .
OK , well , if I could just get a credit card for the reservation .
I 'll pay cash .
OK , we usually need a credit card in case there are any damages .
Take this , please .
OK .
Let 's go get you some sheets .
Some sheets ...
Have a nice day .
That was very kind of you , helping me out back there .
Oh , it 's no problem .
I mean , I figured this whole place is gonna be a parking lot anyway so
if somebody wants a certain room ,
who am I to stop them ?
It 's really no big deal .
Sir ?
Oh , thank you .
353 is where I spent my honeymoon .
Oh .
This old place holds some special memories for me .
It 's interesting ,
come back to a place that feels like you never left .
Almost like you 're right at home .
Don 't you think ?
I don 't know .
Why don 't we get you upstairs .
So , like we said , most of the rooms have been cleaned and stripped
and most of the furniture and linens are in storage .
But lucky for you the owner was too cheap to hire real movers
so all of the beds are still here .
The room might not have the same charm that you remember
but at least you won 't be sleeping on the floor .
That 's alright .
I 'm just here for one last bit of nostalgia .
OK , well , here we are room 353 .
The honeymoon suite .
And if you change your mind
and decide you want to move to a room with a TV , just let us know .
That won 't be necessary .
This is just what I came for .
Thank you so much .
OK , well , enjoy your stay .
( Burps )
If I 'm gonna stay up all night with you ,
you 're gonna get drunk with me .
Cheers .
How ya feeling ?
Better .
Good .
Keep drinking . It always helps .
Hi , Lee .
Hi .
How was your seminar ?
Very good , thank you .
How are you two doing ?
Not bad .
You want a beer ?
No , thank you .
Really ? I heard you were a huge drinker .
Well , we all have our moments .
So , Lee , tell me ... How does it all work ?
How does what work ?
You know , being a psychic and all that .
Well , uh ...
Have you ever been somewhere new
and sworn that you 've been there before ?
Like déjá vu .
Exactly .
Well , if you 've ever experienced what you call a déjá vu
then you have the same God-given ability I have .
In fact , we all do .
It 's just that ...
Well , sometime 's my déjá vu 's happen in another direction .
I can experience certain feelings before they happen ,
but it 's not always clear when or where they come from
so I have to be very careful in ...
What I choose to share .
OK .
Well .
I 'm really tired so I 'm going to go upstairs and go to sleep .
It 's been a long day .
I 'll come find you tomorrow before you leave , Lee .
Don 't let the spirits keep you up all night .
Dude , you didn 't need to say that .
That was really mean .
Oh , whatever . You said it yourself .
She made you feel like an asshole .
Besides , everyone needs a taste of their own medicine
once in a while .
You want another one ?
Yeah .
Alright , you ready ?
OK , this is Claire 's haunted reenactment , take one .
Interior . The Yankee Pedophile .
Wha ... Was that the piano ?
What ?
Was it playing by itself ?
It must be the ghost of Madeline O 'Malley
trying to tell me something .
Show yourself , spirit !
I say , show yourself , spirit !
( Ghost sounds )
There she is .
Poor , poor , Madeline O 'Malley .
( Laughs )
You think she 's prettier than me ?
Honestly ?
Yeah .
She 's a little homely for my taste .
I think you 're much prettier , Claire .
Thank you . That 's nice of you to say .
In fact , Claire , I think you 're one of the prettiest girls I know .
Who are the others ?
Uh ... My mother ,
my sister ,
and that girl that works at the Dairy Queen .
The one with the lazy eye ?
I find laziness very attractive .
I really like you , Claire .
I really like you , too .
No , I mean it . You 're like the coolest person .
I just really feel like we mesh .
You know , I love the fact that you support me with the website
and I just love the fact that you take me seriously .
It means a lot .
You 're great .
Even if I 'm going a little bit crazy ?
You 're not going crazy , you 're great .
I would do anything for you .
Really ?
Absolutely .
Just ...
I like you so much .
Hey . I have an idea .
Me too . What 's yours ?
( Shuffling through drawers )
Let 's go to the basement
and find out what that fucking ghost 's problem is .
OK .
( Door creaking open )
( Inhaler puff )
( Light bulb pops )
That 's a good omen .
Turn the recorder on .
What was that ?
I tripped .
Oh .
Eh .
Sorry .
It 's just the light thing .
- Spider web . - Follow me .
Follow me .
I 'm starting to think we should 've bought breadcrumbs .
Hang on .
I hear something .
It 's weird .
There was static .
I heard that too the other night .
Must be a bad cable .
No .
It 's her .
This way .
( Door opens )
This is it .
This is where they hid her body .
You ready ?
We wish to speak to the spirit of Madeline O 'Malley .
If you are here with us , give us a sign .
Make a noise if you can hear us .
Why do you stay here , Madeline ?
Why does your spirit never rest ?
Whoa .
Madeline . Give us a sign .
( Wind blows )
Did you feel that ?
It 's her .
That was wind .
No , she 's with us right now .
Madeline , speak to us .
We wish you no harm .
Why do you stay here ?
Why does your spirit never rest ?
( Recorder twitches )
( Ghostly sounds )
Wait ! No !
Madeline . We know that you 're here right now .
Speak to us .
( Ghostly whispers )
I can hear her .
Do you hear the whispering ?
( Ghostly whispers )
Madeline ?
Holy shit .
What ?
She 's right behind you .
She 's coming closer .
( Screams )
Luke !
I gotta get out of here !
What ? !
I don 't want to be here any more .
I don 't like this !
What are you talking about ? We just made physical contact !
Why are you freaking out ? !
I just don 't want to be here any more !
That 's it !
Why ? Was it different than the times you saw her ?
There were no other times !
What ? !
I made it up !
I never saw anything !
I made it all up .
I don 't want anything to do with this any more .
This is just too fucked up .
I gotta go .
Luke !
Luke , don 't go !
I 'm sorry , Claire !
You can 't leave me here !
I 'm really sorry .
What am I gonna do now ?
( Knocking )
( Keys jingle )
Lee .
Lee !
Lee ! Lee !
Lee , wake up . I need your help .
Help me .
Lee .
What are you doing in my room ?
Get out of here !
No ! No ! Please !
Please ! Please !
No , I will not you . Please go away .
Come on !
Why should I help you ?
So you can make fun of me some more ?
You know , I believe in what I do .
And I don 't believe in wasting my time on lowly hotel employees
and their insulting ignorance .
Lee , I 'm sorry , OK ?
I should 've defended you downstairs ,
I made a really big mistake , OK ?
But I have a problem .
I 'm scared and I 'm alone , Madeline made contact with me !
I don 't know what else to do , OK ?
I don 't know what else to do !
Is there any more vodka over there ?
Let me check .
Yeah , I found this one .
OK .
Take me to where it happened .
Wait here .
( Ghostly banging )
( Glass breaks )
Lee !
Was it Madeline ? Did you see her ?
Lee , what happened ? !
We must get out of this hotel .
You 're in grave danger . You can 't stay here any longer .
What ? !
I have to go get dressed . Go get your things .
Trust me .
Oh no .
Lee !
I forgot something ! I 'll meet you in the lobby !
Sir .
Sir ?
Sir , I 'm sorry that I 'm disturbing you
but there 's been an emergency
and I have to leave the hotel for a little bit .
Sir , can you hear me in there ?
Sir ?
( Inhaler puff )
( Dull thud )
Oh , shit !
Luke ? !
What are you doing here ?
I 'm sorry I shouldn 't have left you like that .
- Please don 't be mad at me ! - No , no , no !
- Listen , we need to get out of here right now ! - No , no , no , Claire ,
I have to tell you something .
No ! Listen to me , OK !
- Remember the old man upstairs ? - Yeah , yeah ! So what ? !
He 's dead ! He killed himself ! He 's dead !
- What ? - Yeah !
He 's dead !
Did you call the police ? !
No ! Not yet !
And Lee said that it 's not safe to be here any more
and we have to leave right now and I saw Madeline
- and she 's trying to get me ! - OK , OK , wait a second !
Hold on , hold on ! Whoa , whoa , whoa , whoa , whoa .
Come here . Jesus Christ .
Here , sit down .
It 's alright .
His face .
There was blood everywhere .
It 's OK .
Please , please , please just get me out of here .
I don 't want to be here any more . Please .
Alright , OK . Come on . Let 's go .
- Lee ! She 's still upstairs ! - Where is she ?
I don 't know ! She 's getting her things .
Alright , I 'll go get her and you just stay put for a second .
Are you gonna be alright down here for a minute ?
Yeah .
It 's fine . It 's gonna be OK .
Just hold on .
( Ghostly voice )
Lee ? Is that you ?
Lee ?
( Door creaking )
I don 't wanna go back down there .
Are you down there ?
( Ghostly whisper )
( Ghostly hiss )
( Slamming against door )
( Banging on door )
Somebody help me !
( Ghostly voice )
Please !
Somebody help me !
Please ! Please help me !
Please ! Please help !
No ! Please !
Please ! Please !
No ! No !
Alright guys , hold it up
Hold it up .
God . Jesus .
Alright , get her out of here .
I was banging on the door as hard as I could .
I could hear her screaming .
I was screaming for her to open up but she wouldn 't .
She called my name but I wasn 't strong enough to break it down .
This was at the bottom of the stairs .
Alright , listen , I 'm gonna need you to come with us
and answer some questions about the gentleman upstairs .
And help get in contact with her family .
Can you do that ?
- Yeah , I just gotta get my stuff . - OK .
Think you tell the actress to hurry up while you 're in there ?
We need her too .
Yeah .
Oh , listen , you sure you gave me all the names and numbers
of the other guests ?
Nobody you might be forgetting ?
No , I gave you everything .
There was just that other woman and her kid and Ron , the owner ,
but he doesn 't get back from Barbados until tomorrow .
Alright , thanks .
What are you doing in here ?
They 're looking for you downstairs . I said I 'd find you .
We have to go to the police station now
to answer more questions .
Did you hear me ?
I said we have to go .
You knew this was gonna happen didn 't you ?
You could 've done something .
No .
There 's nothing anyone could 've done .
They 're looking for you downstairs .
( Pensive music )
♪ ♪